{
    "id": "6dbc700917034136bbfeff5c4a2c87b2",
    "title": "Active voice or passive voice",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "c32008805af843f9ac81fd15be2043aa",
            "title": "Active And Passive Voice Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "English ………………… all over the world.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "speaks",
                        "is spoken",
                        "has spoken"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The program …………………. by millions of people.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "watched",
                        "was watched",
                        "has watched"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The thief ....................... by the police.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has arrested",
                        "has been arrested",
                        "had arrested"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Wuthering Heights ………………….. by Emile Bronte.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has written",
                        "has been writing",
                        "was written"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The boys ………………… the wounded man.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "helped",
                        "were helped",
                        "had helped"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Football ..................... all over the world.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "plays",
                        "is played",
                        "has played"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Our team ....................... the match.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will win",
                        "will be won",
                        "has been won"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The news .....................…",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "confirmed",
                        "has confirmed",
                        "has been confirmed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The house …………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is painting",
                        "is being painted",
                        "has painted"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "A bridge ....................... by the government.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "built",
                        "has built",
                        "is being built"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}